好了  现在  跳绳准备就绪
All right, now, let me just get my jump rope ready.
你真想让我们冲你打网球吗
You sure you want us to hit tennis balls at you?
是哒
Oh yeah.
为啥
Why?
因为如果你们往我身上打球
Because if I'm really good at
我都能跳得超级好的话
jumping rope while you're hitting me with tennis balls.
那我该是有多厉害啊
Imagine how great I'll be when you're not.
你们真是俩奇葩保姆
You guys are weird babysitters.
等你看我们喂你啥就知道了
Wait'll you see what we feed you.
好了
All right.
灰姑娘穿着...嗷
Cinderella dressed in... ow!
小黄裙...噢
Yellow... ow!
上楼...嗷嗷
Went... ow! Upstairs... ow!
去见...喔奥
To meet... ow! Ow!
嘿  馊主意 馊主意啊
Hey, bad idea! Bad idea!
这是个蠢主意
It was a bad idea!
-叮咚  -你去开门
- Ding dong. - You'll get it.
我去开门
I'll get it.
哇哦
Whew!
一位男士
A man!
我是马丁・马洛伊
My name is Martin Malloy.
-哦  -我是个律师
- Ooh! - I'm a lawyer.
律师
A lawyer?
是有关我妈的吧  她进监狱了没
Is this about my Mom? Is she in jail?
她又去教堂裸奔啦
Did she go to church naked again?
-我不认识你妈  -呃 那就好
- I don't know your Mother. - Ugh, must be nice.
进来吧马丁・马洛伊先生
Why don't you come in, Mr. Marty Malloy?
非常感谢
Thank you.
到底什么事
What's this about?
你俩是不是经营一个叫...
Do you two run a business called...
莎姆和小猫的超级炫酷轻松愉快宝贝看护服务的
Sam and Cat's super rockin' fun-time Babysitting Service?
那又怎样
Why?
看这张纸
Take these papers.
唔 装订好的
Ooh, stapled.
-这是份制止令 -嘿
- That's a cease and desist order. - Hey!
麻烦讲英语
Talk English, man.
好吧  我再说清楚点
Fine, I'll be more clear.
把你们的宝贝看护服务名称改掉
Change the name of your Babysitting Service.
你们无权使用“莎姆和小猫”这个名称
You're not allowed to use the names Sam and Cat.
-啥  -可这是我们的名字啊
- What? - But those are our names.
这也是1970年起就超受欢迎的儿童剧名字
It's also the name of a popular kids' TV show from the 1970s.
什么儿童剧
What TV show?
鲑鱼猫
Salmon Cat.
-什么鲑鱼猫  -这个鲑鱼猫
- Salmon Cat? - Salmon Cat.
这是布偶
That's a puppet.
叫鲑鱼猫的布偶
A puppet named Salmon Cat.
看见没  它是半猫半鱼的
Look, he's half cat, half salmon.
但它是条鱼
That's a fish.
噢  这么个鲑鱼猫
Oh. Salmon Cat.
可我们是莎姆和小猫  不是什么诡异的鱼猫布偶
But we're Sam and Cat, not some weirdo mutant fish puppet.
鲑鱼猫是儿童剧
Salmon Cat was a show for children.
你们两个经营保姆业务
You two run a Babysitting Service for children.
鲑鱼猫  莎姆和小猫
Salmon Cat. Sam and Cat.
很明显会搞混的
Obviously, that's confusing.
真的会搞混耶
It is confusing.
你都能把吐司搞混
You think toast is confusing.
才不是呢  我原来是会搞混
No. I used to think it was confusing,
但自从我读了那本吐司书之后就豁然开朗了
but then I read that book about toast and now I get it.
你们的宝贝看护服务
You girls must stop using Sam
必须停止使用莎姆和小猫这个名词
and Cat in the name of your Babysitting Service.
但这名字已经注册网站了
But it's already on our website
名片上也是  我还定做了T恤衫
and on our business cards. I ordered T-shirts.
小猫
Cat!
我来搞定
I got this.
她拿着个网球拍做什么
Why is she holding a tennis racket?
我猜她要冲你打球
I think she's going to hit you with balls.
慢着  我可是个律师...
Wait, I am a lawyer and I...
瞄准嘴巴发射
Ball in the hole!
噢
Oh!
唔..唔唔
Mm! Mm!
现在我要来个吐司
Now I want toast.
我去拿那本书
I'll get my book.
一二三四五六七八
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
各就各位  预备  走着
Schlemeel! Schlemazel! Hasenfeffer Incorporated.
好吧  等一下  你们是说
Okay, wait a minute, you're saying
昨天一个律师突然来你们公寓了
a lawyer just showed up at your apartment yesterday?
是啊  而且他说我们不能用
Yeah. And he said we're not allowed to use the names,
莎姆和小猫这个名字了
Sam and Cat anymore for our Babysitting Service.
可是为什么啊
But why?
因为原来有个
Because there used to be
愚蠢的儿童布偶剧叫鲑鱼猫的
some stupid puppet show on TV called Salmon Cat.
哎呀  谁想听我讲
Say, who wants to hear about
我当年看鲑鱼猫的快乐时光
the time I was having a salmon dinner at Chasens?
-没人想  -我不听
- Nobody. - Not I.
-好吧  -你好  食物还满意吗
- Well! - Hello. Are you enjoying your foods?
-嗯 很棒 -是的 谢谢你
- Mm, great. - Yes, thank you.
我的薯条还没来啊
Except I didn't get my curly fries.
噢不是吧
Oh no!
对不起我忘记了
I'm sorry, I forgot.
噢 他忘了你的薯条
Oh, he forgot your fries?
就像他忘了我的生日一样
Like he forgot my birthday?
在人类面前能不能收敛点
Can we please not do this in front of the humans?
呃 你俩在一起了吗
Uh, are you two dating?
没有没有
No. No. No.
她不是我喜欢的类型
She's not my type.
圣诞派对上我还是你喜欢的类型呢
I was your type at the Christmas party.
就那么一次
That was one time.
嘿 我想找到了耶
Hey, I think I found it!
-鲑鱼猫儿童剧吗  -应该是 快看看
- The Salmon Cat Puppet Show? - Yeah. I think. Check it out.
嗨孩子们  欢迎来到鲑鱼猫稀奇古怪的世界
Hey kids, it's time for the wet and wacky world of Salmon Cat.
今天的主题是...
Today's episode is about...
分享
Sharing.
呃...这真是..
Ugh, this is...
折磨我
Torture.
嘘  我喜欢看
Shh, I like it.
喵喵喵
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
我有一大袋子糖果耶
I got a whole bag of candy.
哼哼哼
Oink, oink, oink.
你好啊鲑鱼猫
Hi there, Salmon Cat.
你好啊八爪猪
Hi there, Octopiggy.
-能给我些糖吗  -不行
- Can I have some candy? - No.
可我希望你能给我分享些糖果
But I was hoping you would share some of your candy with me.
好了 这垃圾老娘再也看不下去了
Okay, I can't watch any more of this trash.
而且这节目完全
And that show has absolutely
和咱们的宝贝服务挂不上钩
nothing to do with our Babysitting Service.
是啊  这些布偶住在水里面
Yeah. Those puppets live underwater.
咱们可都在水上面看孩子呢
And we always babysit above water.
你觉得我们
Do you think we really have
真的有必要去把名称改掉吗
to change the name of our Babysitting Service?
不  要是我就不担心这张愚蠢的通告
No. I wouldn't worry about these dumb papers.
律师总是整这些繁文缛节
Lawyers are full of mumbo and jumbo.
你确定
You sure?
不确定
No.
噢  我得赶去机场了
Oh, I have to get to the airport.
-你要去哪里  -墨西哥
- Oh, where ya going? - Mexico!
去墨西哥做啊
Mexico? Why?
这个嘛  就是有着
Well, let's just say it involves bikinis,
比基尼  指绘和辣椒的地方啦
finger painting, and hot peppers.
瓜达拉哈拉
Guadalajara.
她在那充满比基尼  指绘和辣椒
What could she be doing that involves bikinis,
的地方能做什么
finger painting, and hot peppers?
噢我的天啊
Oh my God!
她说什么
What'd she say?
没说什么  她向我耳朵里伸舌头
Nothing. She stuck her tongue in my ear.
可我以为马是用来骑的
But I thought horses were only meant for riding.
通常是这样  可我妈当时非常饿  然后就..
Yeah, usually, but when my Mom gets super hungry, it's...
真恶心
Ewe.
嘿 门这是怎么了
Hey, what's up with the Po-Po?
嘿
Hey!
这是怎么回事
What's the situation?
你是谁
Who are you?
我吗 我是佩内洛普...
Me? I'm Penelope...
伯利森
Mumbleson.
-我是小猫・瓦伦汀  -噢
- And I'm Cat Valentine. - Oh!
噢嘿  汉森检查员
Oh, hey, Deputy Hanson.
-你好啊戴斯  -你好
- How are ya, Dice? - What's up?
你认识这个警察啊
You know this policeman?
是啊  我给他搞到了太阳马戏团的票子
Yeah. I got him tickets to Circus Olay.
我喜欢看杂技
I like acrobats.
那么  这个黄封条和大锁是怎么回事
So, what's with the yellow tape and the big lock?
这个嘛  我很抱歉有个律师
Well, I'm sorry, but some
拿着法官的书面通知要封掉你的公寓
lawyer got a Judge to seize your apartment.
-啥玩意  -是的
- Humma? - Yeah.
说姑娘你们在这地方
Says you girls are running
经营一个非法保姆服务
a babysitting business from this address.
卟啦卟啦卟啦
Blah, blah, blah.
然后你们被禁止
And you've been ordered to
用莎姆和小猫这个名称
cease and desist using the name Sam and Cat.
所以  问题解决之前
So, until the matter is settled,
你们都不能再进去做保姆了
you are not allowed to enter your place of business.
-可我们住在这里  -抱歉 去和法官说吧
- But we live in there. - Sorry. Talk to the Judge.
或者你走后我们再闯进去
Or we'll just come back and ordered to break in after you leave.
逗我呢吧你
I don't think so.
因为我会一直坐在那
Because I'm gonna sit right
整日整夜看管这地方
there and guard this place all day and night.
-莎姆  -好吧
- Sam. - Okay.
如果我还是闯进去了呢
What if I just break in anyway?
那我就只能用我的泰瑟枪..
Then I'll just have to use my tase...
卧槽  是谁用香蕉调换了我的泰瑟枪
All right, who replaced my taser with this banana fruit?
-我不会玩那个  -不是我
- I don't play that. - Wasn't me.
给我泰瑟枪
Give me my taser.
给我香蕉
Give me my banana.
呃
Um...
嘿  现在几点了
Hey, what time is it now?
-刚过午夜  -嗯
- Uh, just after midnight. - Mm!
什么...
What the...
快看  我在灌木丛里找到一个新内裤
Hey, look, I found a new pair of underwear in the bushes.
男式的还是女式的
Boys' or girls'?
-男式的  -恶心
- Boys'. - Gross.
呃
Huh.
哈
Ha!
噢噢噢
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
-怎么了  -西尔维亚・伯克和珍妮丝・多宾斯
- What? - Sylvia Burke and Janice Dobbins.
-他们是谁 是人吗  -是的
- Who are they? People? - Yeah.
她们是制作那个
They're the two ladies who
愚蠢儿童剧鲑鱼猫的人
created that stupid puppet show Salmon Cat.
看起来她们现在还住在洛杉矶呢
And it looks like they still live here in Los Angeles.
谢谢你啊因特网  破坏了大家的隐私
Thank you, Internet, for destroying everybody's privacy.
好的好的  太好了
Okay, okay, okay, this is great.
是啊  我们该怎么做
I know, what're we gonna do?
明天  你去见见珍妮丝
Tomorrow, you are gonna go see Janice...
我就去会会西尔维亚
And I am gonna go see Sylvia.
我们就和她们谈谈然后把名字要回来
And we are gonna talk those bichons into giving us our name back!
好耶
Yeah!
怎么回事  发生了什么
What's going on? What happened?
-抱歉  -我们只是...
- Sorry. - We were just...
在下面..
Under.
哪里下面(内裤)
Under where?
-回答正确  -完全正确
- That's right. - Exactly.
非常感谢你能见我  珍妮丝
Thank you so much for seeing me, Janice.
不客气 亲爱的
You're very welcome, dear.
现在  说说你怎么到这里来了
Now, what brings you here?
噢 公交车带我来的
Oh, it was a bus.
不是  我是说  你为什么打电话来见我
No. I mean, why did you call and ask to meet with me?
噢对了  是这样的  我的好盆友和我经营一个
Oh, right. See, my friend and I have this business called
莎姆和小猫的超级炫酷欢乐时光保姆业务
Sam and Cat's super rockin' fun-time Babysitting Service.
哎呦  多有意思啊
Oh! How much fun is that?
-就是啊  -是吧
- I know! - Yeah!
但是有个法官不让我们进我们的公寓了
Except a Judge locked us out of our apartment.
哦
Oh.
因为我们生意的名字
Because our business name
太像你过去的节目  鲑鱼猫
sounds too much like your old TV show, Salmon Cat.
你知道我收集运动球吗
Do you know I collect sports balls?
说啥
Say what?
看  这些墙上
See, these walls are filled
挂满了世界上存在的每一种
with sports balls from every sport in the world.
在运动里使用的球
That uses a ball.
嗯
Hmm.
而且每个球上都有运动明星签的名
And every ball is autographed by a famous sports ball player.
哇哦  我们能谈谈别的吗
Wow, can we talk about something else?
你随便说个运动  我都有那个球
I'll bet I have a ball for any sport you can name.
我不想说来着
I don't wanna name a sport.
-说一个  -网球
- Name a sport. - Tennis.
在这儿
Got it.
-高尔夫  -啊
- Golf? - Ah.
就在这儿
Right here.
曲棍球
Hockey?
曲棍球用的是饼状的冰球  不算运动球
Hockey is played with a puck, not a sports ball.
抱歉啦
I'm sorry.
问我垒球吧
Now, ask me about softballs.
嗯
Um...
-你有垒球吗  -九个
- Do you have any softballs? - Nine.
-再多一个就十个了  -哦
- One more and you'll have ten. - Ooh!
-来个饼干球  -好的
- Cookie ball? - All right.
哦
Ooh.
好吃
Mm.
嗯
然后我就把那条内裤套到那个警察的脑袋上了
So then, I put the underwear right on top of the cop's head.
-你这孩子真有意思  -我还行吧
- You're a funny kid. - Ah, I'm all right.
说回这件鲑鱼猫的事
So, anyway, back to this whole Salmon Cat thing.
哦  什么
Oh, yeah what?
那个律师真的是在难为我和我朋友
That lawyer is really giving me and my friend a hard time.
抱歉  是我邻居的狗
Excuse me. My neighbor's dog.
真好听啊  是吧
Pleasant, isn't it?
如果你们不让那只狗闭嘴
If you don't shut that barking dog up,
我就亲自过去把你的脸撕碎
I'm gonna come up and rip your face off.
喝点苏打水吗
Would you like a soda?
不  谢了
No, thank you.
我在想  你能不能
So I was thinking, if you could just,
额  签张合同什么的
like, sign a piece of paper.
一点儿闲着的时候都没有
All day long.
好吧  如果你们不让它闭嘴
Okay. If you don't shut that dog up,
我就过去
I'm gonna come up with a garden hose...
把浇花的水管缠到你妈的肥脖子上
And wrap it around your Mother's fat neck!
来点奶酪和饼怎么样
How about some cheese and crackers?
这是个棒球
Now, this is a baseball.
是啊
Uh-huh.
你看  是棒球明星泰・柯布签名的
You see, it's signed by the famous baseball player, Ty Cobb.
哦哇哦  我喜欢他的玉米
Oh wow, I love his corn.
那个  关于你原来的节目  鲑鱼猫
Look, about your old TV puppet show, Salmon Cat.
我不想谈鲑鱼猫  它已经是我的过去了
I don't want to talk about Salmon Cat. Salmon Cat is in my past.
我现在的生活主题是运动球
My life now is about sports balls.
但我只需要
But I just need you to...
而且  我不是一个人做出的鲑鱼猫
And besides, I didn't create Salmon Cat by myself, you know.
我知道  你和另一位女士合作
I know. You created it with another lady...
啊啊啊  别说了
Ah, ah, ah. Don't.
别说她的名字  别在我的球面前说
Don't speak her name, not in front of my sports balls.
现在我的室友就在
See, right now, my roommate
和你的老搭档珍妮丝・多布谈话
is talking to your old partner, Janice Dobb...
别说她的名字
Don't say her name.
你没必要大声说出来
You don't have to say it out loud.
-怎么  你不喜欢她  -我恨她
- Why, you don't like her? - I hate her!
我已经30年没和她说过话了
You know I haven't spoken to her in 30 years?
我们只需要你们俩在一块儿
So, all we need you guys to do is get together for, like,
5分钟  同意我们使用我们这个名字就行
five minutes and agree to let us use our names.
我很愿意帮你们  真的  但是
Look, I'd like to help you out, I really would, but...
我的人生啊
That's my life.
那只狗再叫一声  我就上去
If that dog barks one more time today, I'm gonna go up...
噎到饼干了
Cracker stuck in throat!
Cracker stuck in throat.
我来吧
Let me...
非常好
Very good.
都让他鸣咽了
You made it whimper.
那你为什么这么讨厌西尔维娅
So, why do you hate Sylvia so much?
因为我们的木偶节目鲑鱼猫  得了一个木偶奖
Because our puppet show, Salmon Cat, won a Pupper.
哇哦  从来没听过哎
Wow. I don't know what a Pupper is.
木偶奖
A Pupper is an award...
是为了奖励儿童电视木偶节目领域
For outstanding achievement
杰出节目的
in the field of children's television puppetry.
人们很看中这个奖吗
And people care about that?
当然
Oh, yes.
非常风光的时刻
And it was a great moment.
我们终于赢了芝麻街那群混蛋了
We finally beat out those jerks over at Sesame Street.
后来怎么了
Well, then what happened?
我告诉你后来怎么了
Oh, I'll tell you what happened.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
她决定要把奖拿回她家
She decides that she wants to take it home to her house.
哦
Ooh.
然后斯尔威亚说  这是你的节目也是我的节目
And then Sylvia says, it was my show as much as it was yours.
所以奖杯要拿到我家
So I'm keeping the statue at my house.
啊  真是个婊子
Ugh, what a bichon.
然后她就夺走了奖杯
And so then she grabs the statue,
然后我又夺了回来  她又夺了过去
and I grab it back, and she grabs it back,
我夺回来  她夺回去  最后把奖杯抢成了两半
I grab it back, she grabs it back and breaks that statue in half.
哦
Oh!
所以你才这么恨西尔维娅
So that's why you hate Sylvia.
我想把这个拳头
I'd like to take this
塞进她脖子最软的那块儿
fist and jam it in the soft part of her neck.
好的  谢谢珍妮丝
Okay, thanks, Janice.
再见  亲爱的
Bye, darling.
所以你才这么狠珍妮丝
And that's why you hate Janice?
是  我想把这个话筒
Yeah, I'd like to take this
塞进她的大鼻孔
microphone and stick it right up her big nose hole.
-好的  谢谢你的奶酪  -随时欢迎你来
- Okay, thanks for the cheese. - You're welcome anytime.
可真吃了不少奶酪
She ate a lot of cheese.
-嗨  所以  -嘿
- Hi. So... - Hey.
你好  问我新出的猪肉饼
Hello, ask me about our new pork puffs!
没兴趣
No.
我那就在这等到你们感兴趣
Then I'll wait here until you're curious.
我们怎么要西尔维娅和珍妮丝来帮我们
So, how do we get Sylvia and Janice to help us?
不知道
I don't know. All they
她们现在就是想把对方打出翔
wanna do is beat the fudge out of each other.
啊
Ugh!
-嘿  -嗨
- Hey! - Hi.
你去找珍妮丝
I want you to go get Janice
带她4点去搏击馆
and bring her to Punchy's gym at four o'clock.
哈
Huh?
告诉她西尔维娅想和她打架
Tell her that Sylvia wants to fight her.
-打架  -没错
- Fight her? - Mm hm.
我去找西尔维娅
And I'll go get Sylvia
告诉她珍妮丝想和她打架
and tell her that Janice wants to fight her.
我们不能改个名字搬个家吗
Can't we just change our names and move into a new apartment?
-找珍妮丝  带她到搏击馆  -啊
- Go get Janice and take her to Punchy's. - Ah!
你卖出猪肉饼了吗
Did you sell them any pork puffs?
没
No.
很好  现在你知道被拒绝是什么滋味了
Good. Now you know how it feels to be rejected.
我从来没爱过你
I never loved you.
我有点紧张
Oh, I'm pretty nervous about this.
相信我没错
Just trust me.
上周我就相信了你  给了你奶奶的信用卡
Last week I trusted you with my Nona's credit card,
我一不注意  你就买了10磅的蟹腿
and when I wasn't looking, you bought ten pounds of crab legs.
得了吧  如果有人切了你的腿
Come on. If someone cut off your legs,
然后放在沸水里煮
then cooked them in boiling water,
你不希望他们
wouldn't you want somebody
吃的时候蘸点儿黄油吗
to enjoy them with a little melted butter?
珍妮丝和西尔维娅这个年纪根本不能打架
Janice and Sylvia are too old to be fighting.
她们不会真的打架的
They're not really gonna fight.
但我们告诉
But we told them they...
那只是要她们来这儿的借口罢了
That was just to get them to come here.
哈
Huh?
你看着吧
You watch.
她们一看见对方
As soon as they see each other,
就会记起她们过去是多好的朋友
they're gonna remember how they used to be friends.
哦  好吧
Oh, all right.
那个碧池在哪
Where is that bichon?
开打  开打吧
Let's do this thing. Let's do this thing.
好嘞  你想干点什么吗
Okay. You wanna do something?
开始吧  来吧
Let's do it. Come on, let's do it.
我听说你闺女再婚了
I hear your daughter got re-married.
嗯  嫁给了足部医生
Yeah. To a foot doctor.
手足病医生  不错嘛
A chiropodist. Nice.
记得我那个脚趾总是感染吗
Remember that infected toe I had forever?
-臭的那个  -臭的那个  他给治好了
- Ooh. Stinky toe. - Stinky toe. He cured it.
-臭脚趾再见了  -那真不错啊
- No more stinky toe. - That's so nice.
她们很友好啊
Oh, they're being friendly.
嘘  闭嘴下
Shh. Try to shut up.
哦
Oh!
疼疼疼疼
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
哦
Oi.
起开
Get off me!
起来
Get up!
别人打架是不都开始得比这个快多了
Don't most fights happen faster than this?
是啊
Yeah.
这个真是慢
This one's really slow.
啊
Ah!
我好像听到腿断了
I think I just heard her leg break.
不  她的胯而已
Nah. That was her hip.
哈哈
Ha ha!
噢噢噢
Oh! Oh! Oh!
-哦哦  -你觉得什么时候会结束
- Oh! Oh! - When do you think this'll be over?
不知道  她们这么老了
I don't know. They're pretty old.
我们该干点什么吗
Should we do something?
我可以叫个比萨
I can order a pizza.
我不应该相信你
I shouldn't have trusted you.
对  你犯错了
Yeah, you made a mistake.
西尔维娅
Sylvia.
珍妮丝
Janice.
波克
Burke.
多比斯
Dobbins.
好了
Okay.
好了  拿去  拿去  拿去
Okay. Take it. Take it. Take it.
现在你们可以自由
Now you are free to use the
使用莎姆和小猫作你们业务名了
name Sam and Cat for your Babysitting Service.
-太感谢你们了  -也该是时候了
- Thank you guys so much. - About time.
哦  等下  你们对我们这么好
Oh, and wait, we got you a little
我们想送你们点小礼物
something to thank you for being so nice to us.
-哦  -好贴心
- Aw. - Sweet.
小猫在网上某个拍卖网站发现了这个
Uh, Cat went online to some auction site and she found...
1974年的玩具
This toy from nineteen-seventy-four!
哦哦
Oh! Oh!
-天呐  -鲑鱼猫
- Oh my... - Salmon Cat.
我都30年没见过了
I haven't seen one of them in 30 years.
我好多年都没碰过了
I haven't held a Salmon Cat in years.
我要把你带回家  放在我家
I am going to take you home and I am going to put you up on my...
慢着  慢着  慢着
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
谁说你可以带回家了
Who says you get to take her home?
我才要带她回家
I do get to take her home.
你的都是运动球  和这个不搭
You got sports balls. It doesn't match.
不  我要把她带回家  给我
No. I'm gonna take her home. Give her to me.
-给我  -给我  你别伤了她
- Give her to me! - Give her to me! Don't you hurt her.
-给我  -给我
- Give it to me! - Give it to me!
不
No.
啊  天呐
Ah, jeez.
又开始了
There it goes.
我们长大后  你觉得我们会变成这样吗
When we grow up, you think we're gonna be like that?
鲑鱼猫  鲑鱼猫
Salmon Cat! Salmon Cat!
妥妥的
Yup.
我绝不会在远处
I'm never that far.
无论你在哪儿
No matter where you are.
相信吧  我们可以让它成真
Believe it, we can make it come true.
我们按自己的方式往下做  不管别人怎么说
We'll do it our way, no matter what they say.
因为自己的事情只能自己做
Because no one's gonna do it for you.
而我  我  我  我
But I, I, I, I...
我永远不会说  永不
I'll never say, never.
只要我们在一起
As long as we keep it together.
如果你要实现梦想  也深知梦想的意义
If you're living a dream, and you know what it means.
绝对不要让别人改变你的主意
Then you can't let them change your mind.
这就是我们所选择的生活  持续地打破常规
It's the life that we choose, and we still break the rules.
但一切都会好起来的
But it's all gonna be just fine.
一切都会好起来的
Yeah, we're all gonna be just fine.
我们都会好起来的
You and me we're gonna be just fine.
莎姆和小猫的新生活  第一季第十七集
Sam & Cat S01E17 Salmon Cat
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： Eiley  Pixielee
后期  校订： line  liloelva